Hello friends, welcome to your own YouTube
channel.  In this video we will
talk about the companies whose
results have come and some news.  A
lot of reactions can be seen among them on the basis of the news.
ASM list has also come.  We will
also study its circular.  So
before starting the video, I would like to say that if anyone has
visited the channel for the first time, then
subscribe to the channel and definitely press the bell icon.
You can also subscribe to our other channel Business Class.  You
can hit and hold the bell icon.   First of all let's
talk
about Tech Mahindra.  We get to see this company in Nifty 50.
Its quarter 2
results have come.  If we look at the PAT of the company, it has
increased by 4.7%.
Growth of about 5% is also being seen in revenue.
This type of business has
grown tremendously in BFSCI and manufacturing sector.  The total revenue
of the company was Rs 13,300 crore.  Which can be said to have
increased by 4.8% on a quarter-on-quarter basis.  However, it can be
said to be around market estimates.  Also, the
company's PAT has increased by 4.8%.  Which
can be said that 1195 crore ABD has just increased by 15%.  The
company's margins have
improved slightly, which can be said to be a good
thing.  This time the company's margins have been 12.1%
which were earlier around 11.1%.  So
tech vendors can say overall the company's
numbers are mixed.  So
because of this, there is going to be a reaction against this company tomorrow.
Friends, let's talk
about persistent systems.  Its
quarter two results were seen.
This company has got tremendous results.   The
company's PAT increased by 45%.  471
crores.  Beat the estimate.  Strong
margin expansion was seen in this company.  The
awesome numbers have been reported by the Persistent System, friends.
Due to which this company is going to be in a lot of focus tomorrow.  The
PAT reported by the company at Rs 471 crore was against
its estimate of around Rs 436 crore.
Revenue increased by around 24% to Rs 3580
crore.  Eight Eight saw the company's 583 crores.
So, according to every parameter, the
Persistence system has reported tremendous results.
So due to the great news,
this company is going to be in a lot of focus.   The
results of ICIC LBD have also come.  If we
look at its numbers, we can say that it is a decent number.
Beat the estimate.  Net PAT increased by 18%.
Gross premium has increased by 2%.  The
company has also announced a dividend of ₹6.5.  We'll
talk
about friends' stone real realers.
We are seeing OFS in this company.
Its floor price was fixed at ₹550.
Friends, the company is selling its stake worth ₹252 crores.
So we can say that the
goods are being sold by the promoter.  So
due to the OFS news, this company will be
seen in a lot of focus.  So if you
want, you can keep an eye on this also.
DCM will talk about Shriram.
News was seen on this also.  The company has commissioned.
35,000 TPA eco-friendly chemical
plant is visible.  We got to
see this commission happening in Gujarat.  It can be
seen starting.
Due to which it can be said that this company is also
expanding its business.   The
saints will talk about DLM.  Its
quarter 2 results also came.  If we look at the numbers,
Pat Company's profit has more than doubled.
Around Rs 32 crore, which was around Rs 15 crore last year.   The
company's revenue has declined by 20%.  So
revenue has decreased, PAT has increased.  The
company's margins have improved.  Only two things are good,
PAT should increase and margin should improve.   If we
look at other things, we are seeing the company's numbers
overall weak.  So, if you
want, you can keep an eye on this company in the joy of increasing margins.
Whose
reaction can also come on this.
Friends, we will talk about Mishra Dhatu Nigam Limited.
This company has received an order worth ₹306 crore.
Now if we look at the order book of this company, it is
currently seen to be around ₹222 crores.  So this
company is continuously getting orders.  So this company will
now be seen in more focus because of this.
Friends, let's talk
about Ola Electric.  An update was seen in this.  The
owner of the company,
Bhesh Aggarwal, has
hinted that Ola Electric may now
enter the energy storage system as well.
However, there is no official news.
He had only made this one tweet and
because of that such speculations are being made.   It is
estimated that by 2030, we will
see this business of
energy storage system worth up to 30 billion.  For
this reason, Ola
is planning to bet on it.
16 Winery has also announced its quarter 2 results.
If you look at the results, friends, there
are mixed numbers.  Flat number: This company has
not shown any significant growth.  So it can be said that due to this news,
it can also be affected.   The
company's revenue remained around Rs 140 crore,
which was earlier Rs 141 crore.  If we look at brand revenue
sales, it has also decreased.  Also,
if we look at the company's line segment, it has
also seen a decline of up to 7.7%.
So this is a stable number,
you can keep an eye on quality party developers.
In this we are getting news that the
company's performance was quite strong in Q2 FD 26.  The
company is acquiring.
This company is acquiring some prime Pune land.
So because of this, we can say that
this company will remain in a lot of focus.  Also, if we
talk about the sales of the company, it has increased by 9% on
quarter on quarter basis and its
sales volume has increased by 2% to around Rs 670 crore.
So because of this, this company will
also be seen on the radar of the market.   We will also
talk about Thayer.
Results of this company also came.  The
company showed very strong growth in the results.  The company
's PAT increased by 80% and came to around Rs 48 crore.  Apart from this,
we also saw another very important thing of the company in this.  The company has
announced bonus.  If you look at the bonus ratio, it
is 2:1, which means if you have one equity,
you will get two as bonus.
This has been announced by the company.
Due to which Thyro Care company will be
seen in a lot of focus.  The company's
revenue also increased significantly.  A growth of 22% was
seen.  This time revenue of about Rs 216
crore was shown.  ABID rose by 47%.  The
company's margins have also increased from 27.2% to
32.9%.  The
company has also announced a dividend of ₹7.
Due to which Thyro Care company can be seen in a lot of focus.
Apart from these,
results of many companies will be declared on October 15.  In which especially
Jel 1, Axis Bank, Delta Corp
can keep an eye on it.  Results of HDP Finance Service,
HDFC AMC and HDFC L will be declared.
Heritage Foods RFC KEI Industries KSPS
LTF and we will get to
see the results of many more companies.
We will also get
to see the numbers of Muthoot Capital.  You can keep an eye on this also.
Network 18, Nucovist Over
Reality, its results will also come.  Quick Hill
's numbers will be seen.  Rosary Biotech
's numbers will come.  Tata Communication Tips
Mus This company will also release its results.
Energy Global will also see its Quarter 2
results.  So there will be a
lot of reaction in these companies also based on the results.
So you can keep an eye on them too if you want.   Let's
talk about ASM list.  Three
companies were added here whose names are
Cargo Trans Maritime, Neeraj Cement
Structurals, Shiv Tex Limited
and six companies were also removed
whose names are ABM Knowledge,
Bajel International, Dhani Finance, Khyaati
Multimedia Entertainment Ltd, Business
Connection, SP Capital Financing.
Action was taken against three companies in the long term list whose names are Bombay Talkies,
Gujarat, Gujarat Terris Lab and Mizam Ventured.
Apart from these, the price bands of 14 companies have been
changed.  I have 5% of Jel Fibre,
20% of Apts Pharma, 20% of Bharat Drone Airb Innovation,
5% of Cambridge Technology, along with
5% of Naagrika Capital,
10% of Regent Enterprise, 10% of True Colour, 10% of Binin,
2% of Women Network, 2% of Systematic Security, its
price band will be there, so all these companies will be
seen in the news a lot tomorrow,
so I hope friends you
liked this video, if you liked the video then
subscribe to the channel.
Press the bell icon.
Share it with as many people as possible.  Thanks
friends.